<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_stv380_m">
		<text>STV-380</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stv380_m_descr">
		<text>
		The STV rifle, short for Sung Tru?ng Vi?t Nam is a family of Vietnamese made assault rifles. These rifles have all been assembled at the Z111 Favtory and chambered in 7.62x39mm cartridge.\n
		The STV rifles are modifications made to the IWI Galil Ace, this modifications were performed by the Z111 Factory with the main objective of helping the vietnamese soldiers familiarize with the newly military issued rifles, as they were transitioning from the old AK-47 and AKM assault rifles.\n\n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 7.62x39mm compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scarl_m">
		<text>FN SCAR-L (Tan)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scarl_blk_m">
		<text>FN SCAR-L (Black)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scarl_m_descr">
		<text>
		The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. \n
		This family of rifles consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-L (Light) is chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] FN Herstal FN40GL Mk2 grenade launcher\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rsass_m">
		<text>Remington R11 RSASS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rsass_m_descr">
		<text>
		The Remington Semi Automatic Sniper System produced by Remington Arms and JP Enterprises, is designed to fit the necessity of a highly accurate and rapid firing sniper rifle. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 7.62x51mm compatible suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp155_u">
		<text>MP-155 Ultima</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp155_u_descr">
		<text>
		The MP-155 Ultima  designed and manufactured by Kalashnikov Group is a high capacity combat shotgun, designed to provide the user with easy to access information during combat. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mcx_m">
		<text>SIG MCX VIRTUS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mcx_m_descr">
		<text>
		The SIG MCX is a family of firearms designed and manufactured by SIG Sauer, developed to fit many different military categories. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-Monster suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m590a1_m">
		<text>Mossberg 590A1 Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m590a1_m_descr">
		<text>
		Mossberg 590 was developed by O.F. Mossberg &amp; Sons company during 1970s in US as a modification of the Mossberg model 500 shotgun for adoption by the US Military. Modifications included strengthening of the receiver, installation of the vented heatshield around the barrel, a bayonet lug and extended magazine and an aluminium trigger guard instead of plastic one. Standard finish is Parkerizing, and the gun is provided with replacement pistol grip, which allows easy conversion to 'Cruiser' modification. Since 1987, this was the standard shotgun of US Armed forces; officially replaced in US Army with Benelli M1014 semi-automatic shotgun, Mossberg 590A1 shotguns are still used by US Navy and US Marine Corp.\n \n
	    %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_honey_badger_m">
		<text>AAC Honey Badger</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_honey_badger_m_descr">
		<text>
		The AAC Honey Badger PDW is an integrally supressed personal defense weapon based on the AR-15 platform.\n
		This special version has had the integrated supressor removed and completely built 5.56x45mm receiver. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-Monster suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_brn_180_m">
		<text>Brownells BRN-180</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_brn_180_m_descr">
		<text>
		The BRN-180 designed and produced by Brownells, incorporates many of the improvements that the AR-18/AR-180 rifles introduced in the 1960s, including a more robust, reliable gas piston operating system.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-Monster suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_adar_m">
		<text>ADAR 2-15 Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_adar_m_descr">
		<text>
		The ADAR 2-15 is a Russian civilian firearm developed from the AR-15 platform. It consists of Israely components and the barrels produced by Molot Arms.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Advanced Armament (AAC) M4-2000 suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_rgn_impact">
		<text>RGN Hand Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgn_impact_descr">
		<text>
		The RGN hand grenade short for Ruchnaya Granata Nastupatel'naya, is an offensive Soviet fragmentation hand grenade.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]CHARACTERISTICS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Blast power: %c[ui_gray_1]medium\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Blast radius: %c[ui_gray_1]2-5 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Avg. number of fragments: %c[ui_gray_1]75 (small shrapnels)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Explosion delay: %c[ui_gray_1]1.8 seconds\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_rgo_impact">
		<text>RGO Hand Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgo_impact_descr">
		<text>
		The RGO hand grenade short for Ruchnaya Granata Oboronitel'naya, is an defensive Soviet fragmentation hand grenade.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]CHARACTERISTICS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Blast power: %c[ui_gray_1]medium\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Blast radius: %c[ui_gray_1]2-7 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Avg. number of fragments: %c[ui_gray_1]85 (small shrapnels)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Explosion delay: %c[ui_gray_1]1.8 seconds\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type89_m">
		<text>Howa Type 89</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type89_m_descr">
		<text>
		The Howa Type 89 Assault Rifle, is a Japenese assault rifle chambered in 5.56x45mm .\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-Monster suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_famas3">
        <text>FAMAS F3</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_famas3_descr">
        <text>
		FAMAS stands for Fusil d'Assaut de la Manufacture d'Armes de St-Etienne (Assault Rifle by St-Etienne Arms Factory). Development of this rifle began in 1967, by Paul Tellie, a French arms designer. This new rifle was intended to replace the ageing MAS Mle.49/56 semi-automatic rifles, MAT-49 submachine guns and MAC Mle.1929 light machine guns. The first FAMAS prototype had been built in 1971, and French military began to test this rifle in 1972. Meanwhile, France adopted a Swiss-designed SIG SG-540 5.56mm assault rifle as an intermediate solution. The FAMAS was adopted by the French in 1978 and since then became a standard French Army rifle, known among the French soldiers as "Le Clairon" (the bulge).\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp7">
		<text>H&amp;K MP7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp7_descr">
		<text>
		The Heckler &amp; Koch MP7 (Maschinenpistole 7) is a German personal defence weapon (PDW) designed and manufactured by Heckler &amp; Koch (H&amp;K) and chambered for the H&amp;K 4.6x30mm cartridge. It was designed with the new cartridge to meet NATO requirements published in 1989, as these requirements call for a personal defense weapon (PDW) class firearm, with a greater ability to penetrate body armor than current weapons limited to conventional pistol cartridges. The MP7 went into production in 2001.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_descr">
		<text>
		The MP5 is one of the most famous and wide spread firearms of its class. The MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favourite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organisations the world over. The MP5A3 is fitted with a retractable metal stock. Not surprisingly, having flooded the global black markets, it eventually made its way to the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19mm compatible suppressor (after modification)\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble_descr">
		<text>
		A submachine gun prototype based on the excellent H&amp;K MP5A3 model. Designed as a next generation close quarter combat weapon, it benefits from a higher caliber, rate of fire and accuracy.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor (after modification)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_descr">
		<text>
		A variant of the MP5 with an integrated suppressor. In the Zone, mercenaries prefer this variant to the normal one.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Special MP5SD suppressor (integrated)\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_p90">
		<text>FN P90</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_descr">
		<text>
		The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities does not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium, bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_custom">
		<text>FN P90 EFFEN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_custom_descr">
		<text>
		The FN P90 submachine gun was developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon for troops whose primary activities does not include small arms, such as vehicle and tank crew members, artillery crews etc. Standard pistols and submachine guns were proven ineffective against enemies wearing body armour. FN designers developed a new round, initially designated as SS90, to achieve high penetration while keeping recoil low FN used a small-bore approach, creating a round that looked like the scaled down 5.56 NATO round. The result was FN P90 personal defence weapon, introduced in 1990 along with improved 5.7x28 SS190 ammunition which replaced polymer cored bullets with heavier dual core, steel and aluminium, bullets for better penetration against body armour.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ash12">
		<text>ASh-12.7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ash12_descr">
		<text>
		The ASh-12.7 (јЎ-12.7, which stands for "јвтомат штурмовой 12.7мм" or "Automatic assault rifle, 12.7mm") battle rifle is a dedicated CQB/Urban Operations weapon, developed by TsKIB SOO ("Central Design and Research Bureau of Sporting and Hunting Arms"), a subsidiary of the KBP Instrument Design Bureau of Tula, Russia, by request from the Russian FSB (Federal Security Service). The weapon was designed with extreme short-range stopping power in mind because it is intended for special units of the FSB which operate in urban environments against heavily armed and organized gangsters and terrorists who need to be killed in one shot. According to the Russian press, the first batch of ASh-12.7 assault rifles was delivered to the FSB.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 12.7mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mk14">
		<text>Mk 14 EBR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk14_descr">
		<text>
		United States Navy Mark 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle (Mk 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle, "improved combat rifle") - American Marksman rifle, created by special operations of the US Navy based on the M14 rifle. Used by a number of special units of the Navy, including SEAL.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g3">
		<text>G3A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3_descr">
		<text>
		The G3A3 is a battle rifle developed in the 1950s by the German arms manufacturer Heckler &amp; Koch GmbH in collaboration with the Spanish state owned design and development agency CETME (Centro de Estudios Tecnicos de Materiales Especiales). It is designed to use the 7.62x51mm NATO round, and uses a Roller-delayed blowback action. The rifle owes its design to the CETME mod. A, which was designed by the german engineer Dr. Ludwig Vorgrimler. In 1957, Heckler &amp; Koch bought the license to manufacture the rifle, where small modifications were made to the CETME design. Officially adopted into service in 1959, by the Bundeswehr as the G3, it remained in service until 1995 when it was replaced by the G36. Despite having been officially replaced by the German army, it is still in limited use.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig552">
		<text>SIG SG552 Commando</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig552_descr">
		<text>
		The SG 552 Commando is designed for urban combat, making it the most compact member of SIG's renowned SG 550 family, which enhances its CQC capabilities.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m82">
		<text>Barrett M82</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m82_descr">
		<text>
		Barrett M82, in the documentation of the US Armed Forces M107 - American self-loading large-caliber sniper rifle, manufactured by Barrett Firearms Manufacturing and in service with several countries around the world. The automatics of this rifle are based on a butterfly valve. The rifle belongs to the class of "antimaterial", but is more often used as a weapon against enemy infantry.\n \n
	    %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sv98_custom_descr">
		<text>The SV-98 (Snaiperskaya Vintovka Model 1998) is a Russian bolt action sniper rifle designed by Vladimir Stronskiy. In 2003 special operations troops were armed with the 7.62mm 6S11 sniper system comprising the SV-98 sniper rifle (index 6V10) and 7N14 sniper enhanced penetration round. The rifle has been used in combat during operations in Chechnya.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ace21">
		<text>Galil ACE-21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ace21_descr">
		<text>
		The Galil ACE family is designed and produced by the Israeli arms company IWI Ltd. The basis of the ACE Galil rifles is the Galil assault rifle, which in its turn is based on Kalashnikov's AK rifle. The Galil ACE focuses on ergonomics, ease of use and integration with additional attachments, as well as flexibility in combat - the Galil ACE family includes the three most common types of ammunition in the world (5.56x45 NATO, 7.62x39 M43 and NATO 7.62x51), with multiple barrel lengths for each type. This particular variant utilises 5.56x45 NATO rounds and has a compact barrel. In the Zone, this assault rifle is a real rarity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hk416">
		<text>HK416</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416_descr">
		<text>The HK416 is a rifle designed and manufactured by Heckler &amp; Koch to improve the M4. It is available as a complete firearm, or as an upper receiver that fits on any AR-15 type lower receiver. The US Army's Delta Force collaborated with the German arms makers to develop the new rifle. Testing the H&amp;K 416 in 2004 revealed that the piston operating system significantly reduces malfunctions while increasing the life of parts. The project was originally called the H&amp;K M4, but was changed in response to a trademark infringement suit filed by Colt Defence. Currently, it is only available to government and military organisations, hence why this assault rifle is usually carried by Mercenaries.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr25">
		<text>SR-25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr25_descr">
		<text>The SR-25, Stoner Rifle, model 25 was developed by Reed Knight, owner of Knights Armament Co. and Eugene Stoner. The SR-25 is an AR-15 rifle scaled up to shoot 7.62x51mm NATO or .308 ammunition. 60% of parts in the rifle is interchangeable with AR-15 components. This rifle sold well among civilian shooters who needed an accurate semi-automatic rifle in 7.62x51mm NATO or .308 caliber for hunting or target shooting. This rifle also found a favour in US Military. All rifles built on the SR-25 platform share the same basic action, the AR-15/M16 system. Because of AR-15 style recoil buffer, which extends rearwards from the receiver, SR-25 cannot be fitted with a folding stock instead it is fitted with telescoping stock.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] SR-25 special suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] FN Herstal FN40GL Mk2 grenade launcher\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_descr">
		<text>
		The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] FN Herstal FN40GL Mk2 grenade launcher\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_val">
		<text>AS Val</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_descr">
		<text>The AS Val is widely used by Russian Army recon units, as well as by MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry) and FSB (Federal Security Bureau) Special Forces. The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. The receiver is machined from steel forging for improved strength. It has a standard side-mounted rail for optical, night vision or red dot scopes but has no provision for mounting a bayonet or a grenade launcher. The integral suppressor could be easily detached for maintenance, repair, or compact storage, but the rifle should not be fired with the suppressor removed due to safety and reliability issues.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, 1P29, PSO-1M2-01, ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] VSS suppressor (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern">
		<text>AS Val (modern)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern_descr">
		<text>The AS Val is widely used by Russian Army recon units, as well as by MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry) and FSB (Federal Security Bureau) Special Forces. The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. The receiver is machined from steel forging for improved strength. It has a standard side-mounted rail for optical, night vision or red dot scopes but has no provision for mounting a bayonet or a grenade launcher. The integral suppressor could be easily detached for maintenance, repair, or compact storage, but the rifle should not be fired with the suppressor removed due to safety and reliability issues.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, 1P29, PSO-1M2-01, ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] VSS suppressor (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m_mk47">
		<text>CMMG MK47 Mutant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m_mk47_descr">
		<text>
		CMMG Mk47 Mutant, American-made carbine chambered in 7.62x39mm, manufactured by CMMG Inc. Works with all types of AK magazines, including steel, polymer and drums. The carbine has shown exceptional reliability, which, together with the classic ergonomics of the AR system, gives an excellent example of a firearm. This variant features a fully automatic firing mode, for Law Enforcement and Millitary use only. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Hexagon 5.45/7.62x39mm sound suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_descr">
		<text>The UMP was developed by H&amp;K in the 1990s, first appearing on the market in 1999. The idea behind the UMP was to create lightweight and powerful submachine gun, that was also cheaper than the MP5. The UMP, being targeted primarily for US law enforcement, appeared in .45ACP and .40SW chamberings, and later in 9mm. Providing greater stopping power than the MP5, the UMP45 also produces more recoil. This makes controlling full automatic fire more difficult. The UMP45's cyclic rate of fire was lowered significantly to combat this problem.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes, Leupold, March\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vepr101_m">
		<text>Molot VPO-101 "Vepr-Hunter" Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr101_m_descr">
		<text>
		Semi-automatic hunting carbine of 7.62x51mm caliber. It was created on the platform of Kalashnikov machine gun (RPK) and has a similar appearance, weight and dimensions. Designed for professional and amateur hunting of medium and big game, as well as sporting use. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, 1P29, PSO1, ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March scopes\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_5">
		<text>VPO-101 "Vepr-Hunter" 5 round magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_5_descr">
		<text>
		Magazine for VPO-101 and compatible systems, manufactured by Molot arms with a capacity of 5 rounds of 7.62x51 caliber ammo.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_10">
		<text>VPO-101 "Vepr-Hunter" 10 round magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_10_descr">
		<text>
		Magazine for VPO-101 and compatible systems, manufactured by Molot arms with a capacity of 10 rounds of 7.62x51 caliber ammo.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_5_alt">
		<text>Rechambered VPO-101 "Vepr-Hunter" 10 round magazine</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_5_alt_descr">
		<text>
		Rechambered magazine for VPO-101 and compatible systems with a capacity of 5 rounds of 7.62x39 caliber ammo.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_10_alt">
		<text>Rechambered VPO-101 "Vepr-Hunter" 10 round magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_efpwp_vpo_101_10_alt_descr">
		<text>
		Rechambered magazine for VPO-101 and compatible systems with a capacity of 10 rounds of 7.62x39 caliber ammo.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sag545_m">
		<text>SAG AK-545 Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sag545_m_descr">
		<text>
		AK chambered in 5.45x39mm developed by Sureshot Armament Group. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vpo136_m">
		<text>Molot VPO-136 "Vepr-KM" Carbine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vpo136_m_descr">
		<text>
		The Molot Vepr-KM/VPO-136 carbine is based on the well-known Kalashnikov AKM and has an almost identical appearance, weight, and overall dimensions. Designed for hunting of medium and big game, as well as for sporting use. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rd704_m">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-704</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rd704_m_descr">
		<text>
		Rifle Dynamics 704 assault rifle 7.62x39mm, an improved version of the AK system manufactured by Rifle Dynamics. The main difference from the standard AK: the design of the front part shifts the center of gravity closer to the receiver, which significantly improves the controllability of the weapon. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Rifle Dynamics ISG sound suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_t5000_m">
		<text>Orsis T-5000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_t5000_m_descr">
		<text>
		High-accuracy ORSIS T-5000 rifle is an outstanding result of our company designers' efforts. This model was created in cooperation with professional shooters and has the properties required for a customer in the Russian market. T-5000 model is a hand-reloaded repeater with sliding breech bolt and two front locking lugs. It is a multi-purpose weapon. Its specifications provide high-accuracy long-range shots (up to 1500m), high level of shooter's convenience while preparatory, firing and recoil phases, swift sighting line recovery, excellent reliability and ergonomics. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g28_m">
		<text>HK G28</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g28_m_descr">
		<text>
		The HK G28 rifle was developed by Heckler & Koch specifically for the Bundeswehr as a support weapon for small infantry units. The G28 is based on the HK MR308, which, in turn, is a civilian version of the HK 417 automatic rifle. Despite several differences, the HK G28 is 75% interchangeable with the HK 417. This rifle is designed to shoot at distances inaccessible to standard 5.56mm assault rifles. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] AAC 7.62 SDN-6 suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_6x4">
		<text>Bars A-2607 95H18 Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_6x4_descr">
		<text>
			The Bars A-2607 knife, forged of 95H18 steel with a fine wood handle and brass guard.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[d_red] Х %c[ui_gray_2] unsuitable for cutting thick-skinned mutants\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_needle">
		<text>6Kh5 Bayonet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_needle_descr">
		<text>
			The so-called item 6H5 is a knife bayonet adopted in 1989 as a standard issue for use with AK74.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[d_red] Х %c[ui_gray_2] unsuitable for cutting thick-skinned mutants\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_hunting">
		<text>SP-8 Survival Machete</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_hunting_descr">
		<text>
			SP8 is a survival machete made of a single piece of high carbon steel.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] hunting item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[pda_green] Х %c[ui_gray_2] suitable for cutting thick-skinned mutants\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_swat">
		<text>UVSR Taiga-1 survival machete</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_swat_descr">
		<text>
			UVSR "Device for carrying out rescue operations" Taiga-1. A truly versatile survival tool. It is a weapon and a shovel and an axe and everything you can imagine. It was developed and produced in the USSR for various agencies.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[pda_green] Х %c[ui_gray_2] suitable for cutting thick-skinned mutants\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_combat">
		<text>Camper Axe</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_combat_descr">
		<text>
			Universal travel axe for use in field conditions or at the farm.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[pda_green] Х %c[ui_gray_2] suitable for cutting thick-skinned mutants\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_axe3">
		<text>Superfors DB 2020 Dead Blow Hammer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe3_descr">
		<text>
			The hammer is coated with urethane which provides a "thud" using steel balls to cushion the impact and reduce the vibration recoil to the handle.\n \n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
			%c[d_blue] Х %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
			%c[pda_green] Х %c[ui_gray_2] greater reach compared to knives\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m3s90_m">
		<text>Benelli M3 Super 90</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m3s90_m_descr">
		<text>
		The Benelli M3 S90 is a dual-mode shotgun designed and manufactured by Benelli. The M3 is notable for allowing the user to choose between semi-automatic or pump-action operation. Benelli shotguns show excellent ballistic performance, and the finish and fine workmanship are the epitome of traditional Italian style. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] SilencerCo Salvo 12 suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_remington870">
		<text>Remington 870</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_descr">
		<text>Remington 870 is an American gun, first introduced in 1950 by Remington Arms. Due to its characteristic recharge is one of the most famous pump-action rifles in the world. Produced in various versions, it is suitable for both the military and the police, for hunters and athletes, as well as for self-defense.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, C-MORE Tactical, EOTech, ACOG scopes\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m870breacher_m">
		<text>Remington 870 Breacher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m870breacher_m_descr">
		<text>Remington 870 is an American gun, first introduced in 1950 by Remington Arms. Due to its characteristic recharge is one of the most famous pump-action rifles in the world. Produced in various versions, it is suitable for both the military and the police, for hunters and athletes, as well as for self-defense.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Barska ES AC10632, C-MORE Tactical, EOTech, ACOG scopes\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_tx15_m">
		<text>Lone Star TX-15 DML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tx15_m_descr">
		<text>
		The TX15 Designated Marksman Light (DML) series sets the standard for a small frame semi-automatic precision rifle. Utilizing lessons learned during the development of our Multi Purpose Carbine, the DML is optimized for mid-range shooting.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fal">
		<text>FN FAL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_descr">
		<text>FN FAL is a NATO firearm produced in Belgium by Fabrique Nationale de Herstal. One of the most recognized and popular automatic rifles. The FN FAL was originally developed for an intermediate 7.92x33mm cartridge used by the Germans during World War II, then prototypes for the .280 British cartridge appeared. It was later remade chambered for 7.62x51mm NATO, adopted as a single patron for NATO countries. During the Cold War, it received the nickname "the right hand of the free world."\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech, Leupold, March, Mark 8 w/ rmr scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45mm compatible suppressor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_dii_maid_efpwp_show">
		<text>Toggle EFPWP labels</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_sil_ash12m">
		<text>ASh-12 12.7x55 sound suppressor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_sil_ash12m_descr">
		<text>
		Tactical suppressor manufactured by CKIB for ASh-12 12.7x55 automatic rifle.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
